<site>

  <accueil>
    Home
  </accueil>

  <ecoles_partenaires>
	Schools partner
  </ecoles_partenaires>

  <richesses_du_campus>
	Specificities of the campus
  </richesses_du_campus>

  <navigation>
	Navigation
  </navigation>

  <contact>
	Contact
  </contact>

  <campus_hep>
	HEP campus
  </campus_hep>

  <campus_hep_description>
	The new campus of Nantes is based on the interactivity and creativity, which encourages the development of alternative pedagogies. With an area of 4000m², the building has infrastructures that allow  the 1000 students who will work inside to fulfill their schooling requirement in optimal conditions.
  </campus_hep_description>

  <ecoles_partenaires_description>
	There are 6 different schools in the campus. They allow to form in a lot of different job.
  </ecoles_partenaires_description>

  <campus_hep_description>
	The new campus of Nantes is based on the interactivity and creativity, which encourages the development of alternative pedagogies. With an area of 4000m², the building has infrastructures that allow  the 1000 students who will work inside to fulfill their schooling requirement in optimal conditions.
  </campus_hep_description>

  <ecole1>
	First computer school in France created by professionals, EPSI accompanies the development of IT skills for more than 55 years.
  </ecole1>

  <ecole2>
	IDRAC Business School is a business school.  It proposes a lot of formations such as a formation in  marketing and business or in operationnel management.
  </ecole2>

  <ecole3>
	IFAG is a management and entrepreneurship school. It trains business creators or  buyers and all who want to occupy a managerial function.
  </ecole3>

  <ecole4>
	IGEFI - Institute of Management and Financial Studies – is an institution of higher education founded in 1993, that trains high-level professional for accounting professions, management professions, finance professions and pay professions.
  </ecole4>

  <ecole5>
	SUP'DE COM is the first French communication school. It proposes a training course which opens the doors of the market in the services of communication.
  </ecole5>

  <ecole6>
	WIS is a school of Web and digital commerce. It trains professionals capable of supporting the development of companies in the digitization of the business process.
  </ecole6>

  <richesses_du_campus_description>
	There are 6 different schools in the campus. They allow to form in a lot of jobs.
  </richesses_du_campus_description>

  <richesse1>
	Flexible classrooms and co-working spaces
  </richesse1>

  <richesse1_description>
	Students can use flexible classrooms. They can move the furniture as they want to work in optimal conditions as a group.
  </richesse1_description>

  <richesse2>
	IT classrooms
  </richesse2>

  <richesse2_description>
	Classrooms with computers are available for students who have forget their laptop. Theses classrooms give numerous tools valuable for each schools.
  </richesse2_description>

  <richesse3>
	Lunch space
  </richesse3>

  <richesse3_description>
	The room to lunch on the campus is on the ground floor. It permit to the students to eat in a friendly place. It’s also possible to heat your meal thanks to microwave.
  </richesse3_description>

  <richesse4>
	Life and work shared places
  </richesse4>

  <richesse4_description>
	In addition to classrooms, some space are made available inside the campus to work or to chill. Their is a console at the first floor and a ping pong table.
  </richesse4_description>

  <richesse5>
	MyDil laboritory
  </richesse5>

  <richesse5_description>
	MyDil enables the development and development of innovative projects. The lab is dedicated to coding, to technological innovation. You have unlimited access to the latest technologies.
  </richesse5_description>

  <nous_contacter>
	Contact us
  </nous_contacter>

  <nous_trouver>
	Find us
  </nous_trouver>

  <vous_etes>
	You are :
  </vous_etes>

  <votre_email>
	Your email :
  </votre_email>

  <sujet>
	Subject of your message :
  </sujet>

  <votre_message>
	Your message :
  </votre_message>

  <piece_jointe>
	Attachment file :
  </piece_jointe>

  <candidat>
	A candidate
  </candidat>

  <entreprise>
	An entreprise
  </entreprise>

  <autre>
	Other
  </autre>

  <envoyer>
	Submit
  </envoyer>

</site>
